All of this, for now
Until we reach the ideal
I'll reach out my hand
The choice that grows in front of me
The gears of good and evil are moving towards the end of one single thing
Now, come on, cause I'm your choice
And I'm back to the end of life
Until the limits of my body
I'll look at the future
Only one, I don't need anyone else
To be one, I just want to see it
I'll keep my faith and determination in my heart
Highest, highest, I'm the best
I'll go beyond the shadow of my true heart
If you're going to ask me to go beyond the limit of my body, then come here
All of this, for now
Until we reach the ideal
I'll reach out my hand
The choice that grows in front of me
The gears of good and evil are moving towards the end of one single thing
Now, come on, cause I'm your choice
And I'm back to the end of life
Until the limits of my body
I'll look at the future
Only one, I don't need anyone else
To be one, I just want to see it
I'll keep my faith and determination in my heart
Highest, highest, I'm the best
I'll go beyond the shadow of my true heart
If you're going to ask me to go beyond the limit of my body, then come here