I wonder what kind of person you are
Even if you've walked the path you've taken, you're still a human
You're supported by someone, and you live your own way
Your mistakes are
The path you've taken
You can't go back, you can't go back
I couldn't say it well enough
To the hesitation you're hiding
How many times have I been silent?
Because I share your worries and worries
In this world, flowers are piling up
Sadness should have meaning
I'm sure you're strong
You're not the same
You're repeated, but you're still a human
Let's step forward together while supporting someone
With the words of that day
I'll take it, I'll take it
You said, it's okay
Maybe it will come true
I'm always by your side, but I'm scared
Because it's different
These feelings are sparkling
They tell the meaning of the promise
I'm a human, even if I'm weak
There's a place to go back
I'll definitely remember you
I want to be with someone
I'm sure this miracle will happen
I looked up at the sky
I can't see the stars
The tears that float in your eyes
I was definitely trapped
I'm a human, I'm worried
Even if I'm not mistaken on the way I've walked
Because I'm a human
I'm supported by someone
I'm just a human who lives like myself
I'm a human, I'm not limitless
In the dark that continues
If you follow the footsteps, you'll see the future
I'm walking on someone's side
I'll sing with my own hand
Translated by Releska