strangers to love You know the rules and so do I I've filled commitments while I'm thinking of You wouldn't get this from any other guy I just
wanna tell you how I'm feeling Gotta make you understand Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around
And he's hurt you Never gonna make you cry Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie And hurt you We've known each other for so long Your
heart's been aching but you're too shy to say it Inside we both know what's been going on We know the game and we're gonna play it And if you...
Don't tell me you're too blind to see Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around and desert you Never gonna make you cry Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell goodbye and hurt you Never
gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around and desert you
you
We've known each other for so long Your heart's been aching but you're too shy to say it Inside we both know what's been going on We know the game and we're gonna play it I just
wanna tell you how I'm feeling Gotta make you understand Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around
He's hurt you,
never gonna make you cry,
never gonna say goodbye,
never gonna tell a lie.
And hurt you,
never gonna give you up,
never gonna let you down,
never gonna run around and...
He's hurt you,
never gonna make you cry,
never gonna say goodbye,
never gonna tell a lie.